# Manmohan Singh

To build a career in an organization at leading position that will provide me exciting opportunities to utilize my knowledge, skills and experience in such a way so that it adds more value to the organization and help increasing my learning curve.

manmohanrathod421@gmail.com

+91 8384076459

A-400, Durga Vihar, Khanpur New Delhi 110080, New Delhi, India

linkedin.com/in/manmohan0410 in

github.com/ManmohanRathod04



## WORK EXPERIENCE

# **Business Development** Acropolish Pvt Ltd

01/2019 - 06/2019

New Delhi / India

# **Admin**

New Delhi/Wrig Nanosystems Pvt Ltd.

08/2017 - 01/2018

New Delhi / India

# Front end Developer CNS WEB TECHNOLOGIES (P) LTD

12/2021 - 09/2022

New Delhi / India

CNSWEBtechnologies is a service-based company that provides services like Web Design, Graphic Design, Software Development, Bulk SMS, etc to the customer.

#### Achievements/Tasks

 I had front-end design responsibility in this company. And I completed 54 projects and I included some of them in my portfolio.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **BCA**

06/2017 - 06/2021

Higher Secondory School Certificate 04/2016 - 03/2017 (PCM)

Secondory School Certificate 04/2014 - 03/2015

#### **SKILLS**

HTML

CSS

Bootstrap

Javascript

NodeJs

MongoDB

#### PERSONAL PROJECTS

Loan5cr(03-08-22 / 28-08-22 )

- Abs is a loan and funding base company that provides loans such as Home Loan, Business Loan Mudra Loan, etc. I have saved the data in the admin panel with the help of the CRUD operation.
- https://manmohanrathod04.github.io/projectCNSWEB/loan5cr/

#### Ourklient(May-22)

- This is the company's own personal project to manage the day-today operations of leads, sales, payment, etc. I made the front-end part of this project. This project was completed between 12 days
- https://manmohanrathod04.github.io/projectCNSWEB/ourklientc om/

#### CNSWEBTECHNOLOGIES(June-22)

- This is also a company's own personal project which is used to show the services of the company. This project was completed between 20 to 25 days
- https://manmohanrathod04.github.io/projectCNSWEB/cnswebtec hnologies6/

#### Admin Panel(March-22)

- This admin panel project is used to manage customers' data. How
  many customers purchased our franchise, whether customers'
  sites have active or not, whether social links are working properly
  or not etc.
- https://manmohanrathod04.github.io/projectCNSWEB/Adminpanel/

## DVC(Digital Business Card)

- For those customers who could not afford the website, then this
  is a mini site for them, which our customers can give information
  related to their products or services to their customers.
- https://manmohanrathod04.github.io/projectCNSWEB/DVC/dvcn ew/theme1.html
- I have made six themes and you can see by clicking on dbk in my portfolio.

## **ACHIEVEMENTS**

In my previous company, I learned how to finish work in a short time.

I learned the requirements of customers. What do they want on the website?

#### **LANGUAGES**

English

Hindi

Professional Working Proficiency

Native or Bilingual Proficiency